--==本影片由 CMCT 团队 荣誉出品==--
更多精彩影视 请访问 http://cmct.tv
影片压制:梦幻  字幕制作:梦幻  招募Q群:324446465
Allora, come stai, Leone?
Bene.
Okay, okay.Let's talk business.
This fat bastard is moving in
on Morizio's business.
You know Morizio is a reasonable guy.
He just wants a little conversation.
But this guy, he don't wanna hear about it.
Maybe he'll listen to you.
He comes to town every Tuesday.
Are you free Tuesday?
Yeah, I'm free Tuesday.
Nice to see you again, Mr. Jones.
Remember, neatness counts.You got one half hour.
One hour.
Yea... What?
It's Tonto, downstairs.
There's a guy wants to talk to you.
What's he look like?
Serious.
Tell him I'm coming up.
He's coming up.
Somebody's coming up. Somebody serious.
Mickey,
open your eyes. We got company.
We got company.
Come on.
Stop! Stop, man!
Tonto.
Tell the driver to wait for us out back, and hurry up.
Hey sweetie, what's going on?
Don't worry, baby.It's cool. Take a nap.
Oh, my God.
Those fuckers blocked both the exits.
Check the terrace!
911 emergency.
I need help. Somebody's trying to kill me.
Alright. Just stay on the line. I'll just be off a moment.
Sir, I'm gonna connect you with an officer.
Detective Jefferson. May I help you?
I'll call you back.
Relax, man.
I got half of Bolivia sitting in them suitcases.
Hasn't even been cut yet.
Go ahead, take it.It's yours.
Dial this number.
I'll talk to you later, sweetie, okay?
Bye.
Hello?
It's Morizio. Remember me?
I see you're back in town.
Yeah. I mean, no.Just for today.
So it's safe to say today's your last day in town...
and we'll never see your fat fucking face again.
Yeah. Right.
Let me speak to our mutual friend.
He wants to talk to you.
Yeah.
Make sure he understands, and let him go.
Do you understand?
So say it.
I understand.
Good.
Jesus.
Two milk as usual?
Hi
Why did you hide the cigarette?
This building's full of rats.
I didn't want my old man to find out.
Got enough problems.
What happened?
I fell off my bike.
Don't tell my dad about the cigarette, okay?
- Why are you doing this to us? - I don't know...
People got memory problems these days.
It must be the sun.
Know when to come out of the sun.
I don't know how it happened.
What's my job? I'm just a holder.
I hold the stuff you give to me.
I don't look at it or touch it.
I don't know how to cut it.
Try to follow me.
In June, we gave you the dope.
It tests 100 percent pure.
Now it's July, we pick up the dope,
and it tests 90 percent pure.
Somewhere between June and July,
ten percent turned to cut!
I don't know. It's none of my business.
You give me the stuff, I hold it.
That's all I know.
Look, you know, I'm trying to help you out here...
but if you're gonna be a hard-ass about it...
I gotta disturb him.
Let me tell you.
When he's into his music,
he hates being disturbed.
I'm telling you the truth.
I hope so,
because he's got a talent for sniffin' out a lie.
It's scary.It's almost like a sixth sense.
Are you gonna
change your tune
or I gotta bust into his?
I'm telling you the truth.
All right.
Stan.
I'm sorry. He said he didn't cut the dope.
Oh
Of course he didn't.
Just do me a favor.Find out who did by tomorrow.
Noon.
Malky, wait.
I didn't cut your shit.Find out yourself!
What are you doin' out here?
Get inside and do your homework.
I did it already.
Oh yeah? Get inside and help your sister
clean up the goddamn house!
And stop smoking cigarettes!
Time's up. My turn.
Change the channel, and I'll smash your face.
Sorry, sweetheart.
Oh Sweetie
Hi, honey, you two.
Sweetheart, turn that down.
Mama's got a headache.
She took my turn.
She wants to watch goddamn cartoons!
It wouldn't hurt her to move her ass.
I'm not the one with a fat ass around here.
Can someone who's doing nothing all day
but watching cartoons...
move a little ass and go get some food?
I dare you to say that again.
Margie, I think I screwed up.
It wouldn't be the first time.
You always come up with somethin', right?
I think I went too far this time.
You're goin' too far right now.
I'm gonna be late for work.
How about workin' at home today?
Now it's my turn!
Shit! She's gonna hit me! Daddy!
Shit! Shut the goddamn door!
Fuckin' bitch.
Can somebody answer the phone?
I'm busy!
Hello?
This is Marguerite McCallister...
headmistress at the Spencer School in Wildwood, NewJersey.
Is Mr. Or Mrs. Lando home?
Yes, this is she.
Mrs. Lando, when your husband enrolled Mathilda at Spencer...
he told us she had "Problems."
As you know, we pride ourselves on
turning troubled girls into healthy, productive young women.
But if they are not here, there is very little we can do.
Mathilda left school without permission nearly two weeks ago.
I know your husband paid tuition in advance for a year...
but if you will refer to the page 20
in the rules and regulations manual we sent you...
you will see that unless there is a valid excuse
for prolonged absence your tuition will be forfeit.
She's dead.
Tell that fuckin' kid to do a little work around here!
Clean up! I'm tired of this fuckin' mess.
Hurry up!
*Why am I feeling, when things could look black*
*That nothing could possibly go wrong*
*This has been a most unusual day*
*Love has made me see things in a different way*
Is life always this hard,
or is it just when you're a kid?
Always like this.
Keep it.
Hey, I'm going grocery shopping. You want some milk?
One quart or two? It's two, right?
I like these calm little moments before the storm.
It reminds me of Beethoven.
Can you hear it?
It's like when you put your head to the grass...
you can hear it growin'.You can hear the insects.
Do you like Beethoven?
Couldn't really say.
I'm gonna play you some.
Daddy!
You better stay here.
Daddy! Daddy!
We said noon.
I've got one minute past.
You don't like Beethoven.
You don't know what you're missing.
Overtures like that get my juices flowing.
So powerful.
But after his openings, to be honest...
he does tend to get a little fucking boring.
That's why I stopped!
Toss the apartment.
You're a Mozart fan. I love him too.
I love Mozart!
He was Austrian, you know.
But for this kind of work, he's a little bit light.
So I tend to go for the heavier guys.
Cool.
Dude, what the fuck are you doing?
Man, keep your bombacut mouth shut.
Check out Brahms. He's good too.
What the fuck do you know about music?
Man, knock it off!
You check the mattress?
Nope.
- Oh! Fuck! - He's dead.
Stan
Jesus. Look what you did.
Stan, you all right?
Look what you did.
Hey, Stan, Stan, what are you doin'?
What are you doin'. He's dead!
But he ruined my suit.
Yeah, I know, but he's dead.
He's a piece of meat. Forget about it. Calm down.
I'm calm.
- Stay there, OK? - OK
Benny!
Jesus fuckin' Christ, Benny!
It's Malky and Stan!
Take it easy, all right?Come on.
Benny!
Come on, let's get a cigarette. All right?
Benny, we're comin' out!
Benny, don't fire!
Get in there!Jesus fuckin' Christ, Benny!
You wear somethin' new and... Got a light?
Take it easy.
What's happening out there?
It's all right, ma'am. D.E.A. Police.
Leave that poor family alone.
Everything's all right. Just calm down
I am calm. I'm calm.
Why don't you leave them alone?
He said go back inside.
Stan, I think it's better if we go inside.
Benny, turn that kitchen upside down! Find that shit!
Willy Blood, look what you did!
You killed a 4-year-old kid!
Did you really have to do that?
Please open the door.
Please
Benny, there are three kids here.
I think Stan killed this girl.
Willy, that asshole, shot the little boy.
The third one's missing. Find her.
Shit. We missed the little girl, man.
I'm gonna find the fuckin' super in this goddamn building.
- Don't you recognize me - Me, Repugnus, know you
Yo! I found it!
Bingo!
Stan, they found it
I know.
There it is.
There's cops outside. We better go.
It's the cops outside. We better go. You stay here.
What do you want me tell them?
Tell them...
we were doing our job.
What's your name?
Mathilda
Sorry about your father.
If somebody didn't do it one day or another,
I would have probably done it myself.
Your mother, she...
She's not my mother.
My sister wanted to lose some weight anyway.
Bet she never looked better.
She's not even my real sister.
Just a half sister.
Not a good half at that.
If you couldn't stand them, why are you crying?
Because they killed my brother.
What the hell did he do? He was four years old.
He never used to cry.
He just used to sit next to me and cuddle.
I was more of a mother to him
than that goddamned pig ever was.
Don't talk like that about pigs.
They're usually nicer than people.
But they smell like shit.
Not true.
As a matter of fact, right now
I have one in my kitchen that's very clean...it smells very nice.
You don't have a pig in your kitchen.
Yes, I do.
I was just in there, and I didn't see any goddamned pig.
Don't move. I'll get him.
Piggy, piggy where are you?
There you are.
Hi, Mathilda.
Hi, piggy.
How are you today?
I've seen better days.
What's your name?
Leon.
Cute name.
You have anyone to go to,
any family anyplace else?
I'm gonna get some more milk.
Holy shit.
Don't touch that, please.
Leon, what exactly do you do for a living?
Cleaner.
You mean you're a hit man?
Yeah.
Cool.
Do you clean anyone?
No women, no kids. That's the rules.
How much would it cost to hire someone to get those dirtbags...
who killed my brother?
Five grand a head.
How about this.I work for you...
and in exchange, you teach me how to clean?
What do you think?
I'll clean your place. I'll do the shopping.
I'll even wash your clothes.
Is it a deal?
No, it's not a deal.
What do you want me to do? I've got no place to go.
You've had a rough day today.
Go to sleep, and we'll see tomorrow,OK?
You've been really great with me, Leon...
and it's not always like that.
You know?
Good night.
You sleep well?
Good. After breakfast you gotta take off.
Where to?
Not my problem.
Read it.
You don't know how to read.
I'm learning, but I've had a lot of work lately...
so I'm a little behind.What's it say?
I've decided what to do with my life.
I wanna be a cleaner.
You wanna be a cleaner. Here.Take it.
It's a good - bye gift. Go clean,
but not with me. I work alone. Understand? Alone.
Bonnie and Clyde didn't work alone.
Thelma and Louise didn't work alone. And they were the best.
Mathilda, why are you doing this to me?
I've been nothing but nice to you.
I even saved your life yesterday, right outside the door.
Right. So now you're responsible for it.
If you saved my life, you must've saved it for a good reason.
If you throw me out now,
I take it you never opened your door
like you let me die right there in front of it.
But you did open it.
So...
If you don't help me, I'll die tonight. I can feel it.
I don't wanna die tonight.
You're just a little girl, So
Don't take it badly, but I don't think you could do it.
I'm sorry.
How's that?
Mathilda, don't you ever do that again or I'll break your head.
- You got that? - Okay.
I don't work like that. It's not professional.
There is rules.
Okay.
And stop saying "Okay" All the time OK?
Good.
You expect to use that in this hotel?
Mister, I have to use it...
because I have an audition at Juilliard next month
and I have to practice.
Okay, but not after 10:00.
Okay, I promise.
All right.I'll put you at the end of the hall...
so that you don't disturb anyone.
Fill those out, please.
Daddy,
can I please fill them out?
You know how I like to check in to hotels.
Thanks, Pop. I'll bring these back in a minute.
The fourth floor!
Thanks, mister!
You're lucky to have a little girl
that's interested in things.
I have a kid, 17, does nothing all day long.
Can I leave my plant here
while I take my stuff upstairs?
Of course.
I'm putting in a name of a girl in my class who makes me sick.
If things get hot, she'll take the heat.
There. Finished.
How old are you?
Eighteen.
Eighteen?
Want to see my license?
No. You just look a little younger.
Thanks.
Leon, I want you to teach me how to be like you.
- I want to be strong and smart like you. - Mathilda
I know I'm not strong enough yet...
but I could learn the basics, the theory.
What do you think? Just the theory.
I need this, Leon.I need time to get my head together.
Yeah, and I need...
a drink.
Don't move. I'll go get one.
When you told me to get this baby out for you...
I thought my hearin' was goin'.
I says to myself, " Leon's a pro.
Nobody uses that except beginners."
I like to stay in shape.
Sure.
Always stay on top of it.It's like me.
I gotta know where everything is all the time.
That's why I never leave this place, except to go from here to there.
Change ain't good, Leon. You know?
Yeah.
Check it.
Make sure it's the right thing.
I trust you.
One thing's got nothin' to do with the other.
Remember that.
I will.
The rifle is the first weapon you learn how to use...
because it lets you keep your distance from the client.
The closer you get to being a pro...
the closer you can get to the client.
The knife, for example,
is the last thing you learn.
Okay?
Okay.
Position.
No.
Never take it off until the last minute.
It reflects light.
They can see you coming from a mile away.
And always dress down.
Never brighter than the floor, okay?
Okay.
Let's practice now. It's the best way to learn.
Who should I hit?
Whoever.
I'll be with you in a second.
Give me a few minutes.
Thank you.
You guys get lost. I don't want to see you.
This has to look natural.
No women, no kids. Right?
Right.
Jogger in the yellow and orange?
Okay.
Keep calm.
Don't take your eyes off him.
Breathe easy.
Watch his movement.
Pretend you're running with him.
Try to feel his next movement.
Take a deep breath. Hold it.
Now.
I'm all right. I'm fine.
Get down!
One shot. Not bad, huh?
Can we try with real bullets now?
Not today. Let's pack up.
Like that.
No, thanks.
No discussion.
"It seemed to Socrates..."
I'll do it.
Leon, all we do is work.
We need a break. Let's play a game.
What kind of game?
I have this great game.
It makes you think and helps your memory.
It's exactly what you need.
Okay.
Who is it?
I don't know.
Moustache.
No.
Gene Kelly?
Good.
Your turn now.
Okay, pilgrim.
Clint Eastwood?
I don't know. I give up.
John Wayne.
I was just about to say that.
I swear. It's amazing.Leon, really brilliant.
Amazing
You love your plant, don't you?
It's my best friend.
Always happy. No questions.
It's like me, you see.No roots.
If you really love it, you should plant it
in a park so it can have roots.
Leon
You should be watering me if you want me to grow.
You're right.
They gotta be jumping out of the plate. They gotta be alive.
It's been a long time, Leon.
I missed you.
And you missed some nice jobs too.
Been training.
Training's good, but don't overdo it.
Training don't pay as good as working, Leon.
Tony...
all the money I make, that you keep for me...
You need some money?
Just curious.
I've been working a long time...
and I haven't done anything with my money.
I thought maybe someday
I could use it.
You met a woman.
You gotta be careful with women.
Remember when you arrived in this country?
When I took you in,
you were still wet behind the fuckin' ears...
and, already, you were in deep shit because of a woman.
Don't forget that, Leon.
I wish I could sometimes.
You know, about my money...
Maybe I could give a little
to someone.
You know, to help out.
It's your money. I'm just holding it for you, like a bank.
Except better than a bank
because banks always get knocked off.
No one knocks off old Tony.
Besides, with a bank...
there's always tons of forms and all that shit.
But old Tony, nothin' to read,
nothin' to write.
It's all in his head.
I know how to read now.
That's good, Leon, good.
Your money's here. Whenever you want it,
you just ask me.Here's a grand.
- Come on. - It's okay. I don't need it.
Take it. Have some fun. Go ahead.
Thank you.
All right.
Now let's talk business.Don't move.
I'll go get the file.
Manolo, a glass of milk for my friend Leon here.
Listen, Mathilda, you better be careful.
You can't just speak to any guy off the street.
Leon, get a grip. What's the big fucking deal?
I was just smoking a butt while I was waiting.
I want you to stop cursing.
You can't talk to people like that all the time.
I want you to make an effort to talk nice.
And I want you to stop smoking. It will kill you.
Okay
Stay away from him. He looks like a weirdo.
I'll be out in five minutes. Stand where I can see you.
Okay
Leon, I think I'm kinda falling in love with you.
It's the first time for me, you know.
How do you know it's love if you've never been in love before?
Cause I feel it.
Where?
In my stomach.
It's all warm.
I always had a knot there, and now it's gone.
Mathilda, I'm glad you don't have a stomachache anymore.
I don't think it means anything.
I'm late for work. I hate being late for work.
Hey, How's the practicing going?
How are we today, miss?
A little sick of practicing.
I understand.
But you're doing all right.
I haven't received any complaints.
I put a cloth over the strings to lessen the noise.
That's very smart.
Not everyone loves music.
I know.
What exactly does your father do?
He's a composer.
That's wonderful.
Except he's not really my father.
He's my lover.
Think I'll go for a walk.
What are you doing Saturday night?
What about dinner?
Where you goin'?
Visiting friends at 6J.
Go ahead.
We know you're a busy man.
We'll make this short.
If you'll just take us step-by-step
through exactly what happened.
The guy was here. He went for his gun.
Bang, we shot him.
Where exactly were the kids?
I don't know!
They should have been at school, don't you think?
Your statement said you were the first man in.
Didn't you see any kids?
The door was broken. What happened?
Did you follow the procedure?
I lost a good man here.
What the fuck do you want with me?
Cooperation.
I haven't got time for this Mickey Mouse bullshit!
You want cooperation? Come up in my office, room 4602.
Kids should be at school.
Come on, that's my ball!
Give that back. Where you goin'?
Damn! Where you goin', man? That's my ball!
Follow the blue car.
You want me to blast the music and go through the lights?
No, drive slowly.
Take the hundred bucks, and shut the fuck up.
I do not want to fight you, but you leave me no choice.
Boy, you just gave me a great idea!
I mean a big one!
Welcome back to E! News Daily...
our 30-minute look at the latest in entertainment news.
I'm Bianca Ferrar.
It's for you. A present.
Do you want me to open it? I'll open it.
How do you like it? Nice, eh?
Mr. McGuffin?
Can I have a word with you?
Here. It's for a contract. Twenty grand, right?
His name is Norman Stansfield, and he's in room 4602...
in the D.E.A. Building, 26 Federal Plaza.
I'm not taking it.
Why not?
It's too heavy. Well.
Will you rent me your gear for the day?
I never lend out my gear.
But you still have your gun. Use it.
Just do me a favor. Don't shoot out the window.
Why are you so mean to me?
Wildly killing people you don't give a shit about...
but you won't get the bastards that killed my whole family?
Revenge is not good once you're done.
Believe. It's better to forget.
Forget? After I've seen the outline
of my brother's body on the floor...
you expect me to forget?
I want to kill those sons of bitches.
Blow their fucking heads off.
Nothing's the same
after you've killed someone.
Your life is changed forever.
You have to sleep with one eye open for the rest of your life.
I don't give a shit about sleeping, Leon.
I want love or death.
That's it.
I want death.
Get off my case, Mathilda. I'm tired of your games.
There's this really great game, Leon.
Makes people nicer. Starts them thinking.
The kind of game you love.
If I win you keep me with you for life.
And if you lose?
Go shopping alone, like before.
You're gonna lose, Mathilda.
There's a round in the chamber. I heard it.
So what?
What's it to you if I end up with a bullet in the head?
Nothing.
I hope you're not lying, Leon.
I really hope that deep down inside there's no love in you.
Because if there is just a little bit of love in there for me...
I think that in a few
minutes you'll regret you never said anything.
I love you, Leon.
I win.
I took a hit. I need a hand now.
I know she's young, but she learns fast.
Kids need to be shaped into something, right?
I know. I taught you that.
But ain't there an age limit?
She's 18.
Really?
How about something to drink, Tony?
Sure. Manolo, glass of milk for Leon.
Nice tattoo.
Manolo, make that two.
What's that for?
Can't afford to catch cold.
First you find out where the chain is.
You can't see it, but you can feel it. Here.
I'll ring, you start talking.
What do I say?
Whatever you want.
Yes?
It's Susan.
I'm sorry. You must have the wrong door, little girl.
I don't know any Susan.
Move back a little. I can't see anything.
The light's out. It's all dark out here.
Mister, I'm scared.
Okay.
What the fuck are you doing?
Open up.
If it leaves your mouth, I'll pull the trigger, capisce?
Here's okay. Let it go. I said, "Let it go."
Move. Move over.
Easy. Easy.
Go ahead. Your turn.
Help me. Please don't beat me.
Sir?
Sir, it's not my dope.
Sir, look l...
A little left, please. Sir, look l...
Now, the security shot.
No, the second goes higher on the chest.
Aim for the heart and lungs.
There. Right there. You see?
The first shot takes him out of order.
The second finishes him off.
Never in the face.
If they can't recognize the client, you don't get paid.
You could take out anybody and said you did the job.
Got it?
Got it. Never in the face.
Now you can put the tools away.
What the fuck is going on? Hey, mister!
What are you fuckin...
You see, when you use the silencer a lot...
you have to put a piece of cloth here...
because it gets very hot and could burn it inside.
Okay
A damp, black cloth is the best.
What you doing?
We said no women, no kids.
Who do you think this is gonna kill, junkies and monkeys?
Now it's clean.
Let's get out of here.
I thought we don't have the right to drink.
I know, but we're making an exception for your first time.
Well, if we're making exceptions for a job well-done...
how about a kiss, like in the movies?
No.
Yes.
What you doing?
I'm going to kiss you.
I want you to stop, please.
Come on. Just a kiss.
Stop. Everyone is watching us. Go sit down.
Enjoy.
You don't believe me, do you?
How's that?
When I say I'm in love with you.
Mathilda, please drop it. Just change the subject, okay?
Okay. Okay. Sorry.
So, how old were you when you made your first hit?
Nineteen.
Beat you.
What you doing?
Can't afford to catch a cold.
There's no doorbell.
So knock on the door.
Yes?
Hi. I'm looking for Mr. Reuben's apartment...
but it's all dark out here in the hall, and I'm lost.
Just a second.
You want more? Come on. Show your fucking face.
You think you're going to get me that easily?
When it's tough like this, you know it's gonna be ugly.
Better make it quick or
else we'll be all day listening to his crap.
Asshole! Come on, show me your fucking face, faggot!
Come on, gum trick.
Hey,What about the ring trick? You know that one?
Ring trick? Come on, asshole. I'm waiting.
Show it to me, motherfucker.
That's the ring trick.
Mario, go back to the barbershop. We'll finish later.
Hey Leon, what's up?
All done already?
No.
Nicer than people, eh?
I told you that.
You got a problem?
No.
Get the chair. Sit down.
I was thinking.
If something happens to me someday...
Hey, Leon, nothing's gonna happen to you.
You're indestructible. Bullets slide off you.
You play with 'em.
Tony, I thought about my money.
You remember the girl who came here the other day?
Yes.
Her name is Mathilda.
If anything happens to me...
I'd like you to give her...
my money.
You can count on me, Leon.
Thank you, Tony.
I won't be long.
Did I do something wrong?
No. This one is too big.
Yeah, and I only get the leftovers, is that it?
Mathilda, since I met you everything's been different.
So I just need some time alone.
You need some time to grow up a little.
I finished growing up, Leon. I just get older.
For me it's the opposite. I'm old enough.
I need time to grow up.
Shit.
Come on! Hustle!
- Good shot. - Come on.
You're new, aren't you? Fifth floor, right?
You can't sit here like that.
Really, why not?
Nothing's free. Like a parking meter.
When you stop, you pay.
It's the law.
Only on T.V.
What do you say?
Forget it. How much is your meter?
Ten dollars a month.
Got change?
Don't worry about it. We'll do ten for twelve.
I'll pay now for the rest of the year.
Okay, a year.
Does paying rent here mean
- I have to put up with you guys? - Er, no.
So go play somewhere else.
I need to think.
Stand up. Don't you like your job?
Food.
Where you going?
Special delivery, room 4602.
Sign here.
Have a nice weekend, girls.
Special delivery? Let me guess.
Chinese?
Thai, maybe?
I've got it. Italian food.
What's your name, angel?
Mathilda.
I want you to put the sack on the floor.
Good.
Now I want you to tell me
everything you know about Italian food.
Don't forget the name of the chef who fixed it for me.
Nobody sent me. I do business for myself.
So this is something personal, is it?
What filthy piece of shit did I do now?
You killed my brother.
I'm sorry.
- And you wanna join him? - No.
It's always the same thing.
It's when you start to become really afraid of death...
that you learn to appreciate life.
- Do you like life, sweetheart? - Yes.
That's good.
Because I take no pleasure
in taking a life
if it's from a person who doesn't care about it.
Stan,
I've been looking all over for you. I checked upstairs...
What? I'm busy.
It's Malky, man. He's dead.
Malky was makin' a buy for us from the Chinaman.
But they got nothin' to do with it.
They told me this guy came from the outside.
He was a pro.He was fast. He fuckin' came out of nowhere.
Boom, shoots the Chinaman dead in two seconds.
Easy, man. I'm a cop.
Then turns around, says something to Malky like...
No women, no kids.
I think it was somethin' personal.
Death is
whimsical today.
Blood,
do you hear me?
Yeah, I hear you, Stan. Just chill out, man.
Would you take her up to my office?
All right, yeah.
Jesus fucking Christ.
"Leon, my love.
I know where to find the guys who killed my brother.
Their boss is Norman Stansfield.
He's in the D.E.A. Building, room 4602.
I'm gonna do them myself. If something goes wrong,
I left you 20 grand on the table.
It's for a contract. Five grand a head, right?
I know I'll feel better after I do this.
I love you. Mathilda.
Wait for me. I won't be long.
I can't park in front like this. It's a federal building!
He's gonna do the same exact thing that I said.
A nine "Millie".
Bullets.Another nine "Millie".
What'd you plan to do with all these guns?
Maybe she was planning on taking out the whole building.
Holy shit! What we got here? Lunch.
Careful, Blood, might be poisoned.
No,man.There's no anchovies on this.
Is that what you call 'I won't be long'?
I been hanging around here for at least ten minutes.
I did my best.
Do you like it?
Yes.
So say it.
I like it.
Not thirsty?
You know, a girl's first time is very important.
It determines the rest of her life sexually.
I read that once in one of my sister's magazines.
My girlfriends told me they hated their first experience.
That's because they didn't love the guys.
They just did it to show off.
Afterwards, they started liking it, like cigarettes.
Will I like it the first time?
Mathilda, no.
Why not?
I just can't.
You love someone else?
No.I mean...
There was someone a long time ago.
Before I came to the States.
Her father didn't want her to see me.
She was from a very respectable family.
Mine was...
you know...
not so respectable.
Her dad went nuts every time she'd take off to see me.
She still snuck off to see you, right?
Right.
See, nothing can stop love, Leon.
He killed her.
One shot through the head.
They kept him in jail for two days, and they let him go free.
They said it was an accident.
So...
one night I waited for him.
Five hundred feet with a lens.
He also had an accident.
The same night I took a boat and came here...
to meet up with my father who was working for Tony.
I was 19.
Since then I've never left the city, and...
I've never had another girlfriend.
You see, Mathilda...
I wouldn't be a good lover.
Okay.
Would you do me one favor?
What?
I'm sick of watching you sleep on your chair.
We're gonna share the bed.
I don't think it's a good idea.
It's okay.Put your legs up on the bed.
Yeah. That's nice.
Put your head down. It's okay. Relax.
Good night, Leon.
Good night.
Manolo, take the kids in the kitchen.
I have a lot of respect for your business, Tony.
When you've killed for us in the past...
we've always been satisfied.
That's exactly why today
is going to be very hard for me.
I hope you'll excuse my mood.
My man was killed right here on your turf.
The Chinks tell me that the hit man...
was kind of the Italian type.
So we figured that Tony might know something.
Wait.
There's more.You're gonna love this.
A few hours later, a little 12-year-old girl
comes into my office armed to the teeth,
with the firm intention
of sending me straight to the morgue.
Do you know who came and got her in the middle of the afternnon right there
in my building?
The very same Italian hit man.
I'm dying to meet him.
Relax. Everything's fine.
Sleep well?
I never really sleep.
Got one eye open always.
Yeah, I forgot.
I never saw someone
with one eye open snore so much.
I snore?
Like a baby.
I'm gonna get some milk for breakfast. I won't be long.
Don't forget the code when you come back.
Two knocks, then one, and two knocks again. Right?
Right.
Hello, Signore. Ring these up. I'm gonna go get some milk.
From here on out, you don't make a sound.
You answer my questions by nodding yes
or shaking your head no. You got it?
Is he alone?
Does he expect you?
Do you have keys to the apartment?
Is there a code, a way of knocking, so he knows it's you?
Alpha team.
Final position. We're ready to go.
Be careful.
Move! Move!
Shit.
Alpha team. Man down. Man down.
I told you.
Benny.
Bring me everyone.
What do you mean, "Everyone"?
Everyone!
Take this.
Go take a look.
Don't move.
Do you see anything?
It's the guy.
He's here. He's got a gun to my head.
Ok. Nobody moves.
Let the girl go.
Take it easy, man!
Okay, the girl's comin' out.
Let the girl go.
Grab the axe off the wall. Over there. Go!
You're coming with us.
Christ, he shot him!
Bastard!
Move! Move! Move! Move!
Shut the fucking water off!
Got it.
Come
We're in a bad way here.
Send the cats.I repeat,sent the cats.
I don't know what happened.
I didn't see 'em coming, I swear!
I just went shopping
and I came back, and they were everywhere.
Stay away from the window.
Leon.
Come here.
Snipers.
Okay, now, get this fucking asshole out of there.
How are we gonna get outta here now?
Leave it to me. We're checking out.
But Leon it's not big enough for you.
It's barely big enough for me.
We said no discussion.
No, I'm not letting...
I'm not going! I won't go!
Listen to me.
We have no chance together.
But if I'm alone, I can do it.
Trust me. I'm in good shape, Mathilda.
I know I've got a lot of money with Tony, a lot.
We'll take it and leave together,
just the two of us.Okay? Go.
No! You're saying that so I won't worry.
I don't wanna lose you, Leon.
You're not gonna lose me, Mathilda.
You've given me a taste for life.
I wanna be happy, sleep in a bed, have roots.
You'll never be alone again.
Please, go now, baby. Go.
Calm down. Go now. Go.
See you at Tony's. I'm gonna clean them all.
Tony's in an hour.
I love you, Mathilda.
I love you, too, Leon.
Hey, what the fuck is going on up there?
I just said "Take the guy out", not the fucking building.
We've got one breathing here!
Get a medic on the horn!
We've got a wounded man. Make way!
Down those stairs.
Let's go! Move!
Get that guy off the stairs! Lay him on the layer.
Get your team back out there!
We've got two men comin' down the stairs. Let's hurry!
You okay? Hey, I need a medic over here!
Move your fuckin' asses.
Squad Number One, what's the status on the apartment?
Can't see shit. Too much smoke.
Give us five minutes.
Okay. You got it.
What? Two hundred men
can't find one man and a girl? Did you find the girl?
Hi, how are you doing? Take your mask off, quick.
Let me see you. That's deep. Right. And this one here...
You're from the 3rd Precinct?
Let's open up his sleeve a little bit.
All right, fine. Put it down. This one.
You stay there for two minutes. I'll be right back.
Let me put the mask back on. I breathe better with it.
OK. You're all right. Sit tight.
Come on, everybody out!
Let's go! Out!
Clear the way, men.
What are you doing here? Get out. Come on.
Stansfield?
At your service.
This is from...
Mathilda.
Shit.
Leon asked me to help you out if somethin' happened,
and I think somethin' happened, right?
He put aside a little cash for you.
So what I'm suggesting is that...
seein' as how you're still so young...
I should hold the money for you until you're older.
Like a bank, you know, except...
it's better than a bank 'cause banks always get knocked off.
No one knocks off old Tony.
But it's your money. In the meantime...
all you gotta do is come here every once in a while...
and I'll dish it out so you can have a little fun, OK?
Here's a hundred bucks to start.
Can't I get a job instead?
A job?
What the hell can you do?
I can clean.
I ain't got no work for a 12-year-old kid...
so get it out of your goddamn head!
It's over! The game's over!Leon's dead!
You hear me?
Come on. You think I ain't hurtin' too?
But he's dead.
You're gonna forget all this craziness
and get your little ass back to school, capito?
Now take this money and get the hell outta here.
Don't let me see your face till next month...
'cause something tells me
I'm about to lose my famous kind streak.
My parents...
died in a car accident four weeks ago.
It was terrible.
We didn't have the time
to get to know one another when you first came here...
but I want you to know
I'm not the kind of woman who'd let down a child...
whatever her situation, whatever her mistake.
So I'm going to help you
and do my best to welcome you here again.
But on one condition:
You have to stop lying to me, Mathilda.
I want you to take a chance and trust me.
Now tell me what happened to you.
Okay.
My family got shot down by D.E.A. Officers...
because of a drug problem.
I left with the greatest guy on Earth.
He was a hit man, the best in town,
but he died this morning.
If you don't help me,
I'll be dead by tonight.
You know her?
I've never seen her.
I think we'll be okay here.Leon.
*He deals the cards as a meditation And those he plays never suspect*
*He doesn't play for the money he wins He doesn't play for respect*
*He deals the cards to find the answer The sacred geometry of chance*
*The hidden law of a probable outcome The numbers lead a dance*
*I know that the spades are the swords of a soldier*
*I know that the clubs are weapons of war*
*I know that diamonds mean money for this art*
*But that's not the shape of my heart*
*He may play the jack of diamonds He may lay the queen of spades*
*He may conceal a king in his hand While the memory of it fades*
*I know that the spades are the swords of a soldier*
*I know that the clubs are weapons of war*
*I know that diamonds mean money for this art*
*That's not the shape of my heart*
*And if I told you that I loved you*
*You'd maybe think there's something wrong*
*I'm not a man of too many faces The mask I wear is one*
*Those who speak know nothing And find out to their cost*
*Like those who curse their luck in too many places*
*And those who fear are lost*
*I know that the spades are the swords of a soldier*
*I know that the clubs are weapons of war*
*I know that diamonds mean money for this art*
*But that's not the shape of my heart*
*That's not the shape of my heart*